{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899235469","data":{"timestamp":" 946899235469"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 0022e36c-b0fc-4d3d-9fee-6c699883c12b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.116","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899241309","data":{"timestamp":" 946899241309"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 0022e36c-b0fc-4d3d-9fee-6c699883c12b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899250377","data":{"timestamp":" 946899250377"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899250626","data":{"timestamp":" 946899250625"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899251520","data":{"timestamp":" 946899251519"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899252021","data":{"timestamp":" 946899252020"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899252594","data":{"timestamp":" 946899252594"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYUMBA"," userResponse":" VYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899253506","data":{"timestamp":" 946899253506"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOGO"," userResponse":" VIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899254632","data":{"timestamp":" 946899254632"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899255526","data":{"timestamp":" 946899255525"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAANZA"," userResponse":" WANAANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899256349","data":{"timestamp":" 946899256349"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKUWA"," userResponse":" KUTOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899256637","data":{"timestamp":" 946899256636"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899257429","data":{"timestamp":" 946899257428"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899260125","data":{"timestamp":" 946899260125"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899260327","data":{"timestamp":" 946899260327"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899261187","data":{"timestamp":" 946899261186"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWITUNI"," userResponse":" MWITUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899262028","data":{"timestamp":" 946899262028"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIANZA"," userResponse":" WALIANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899262699","data":{"timestamp":" 946899262699"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFIKA"," userResponse":" KUFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899263333","data":{"timestamp":" 946899263333"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899263907","data":{"timestamp":" 946899263907"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899265230","data":{"timestamp":" 946899265229"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAOGOFYA"," userResponse":" KUWAOGOFYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899268336","data":{"timestamp":" 946899268335"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama hawa walikula mimea yao yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899268814","data":{"timestamp":" 946899268814"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama hawa walikula mimea yao yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWA"," userResponse":" HAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899269679","data":{"timestamp":" 946899269678"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama hawa walikula mimea yao yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKULA"," userResponse":" WALIKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899270352","data":{"timestamp":" 946899270351"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama hawa walikula mimea yao yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMEA"," userResponse":" MIMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899270903","data":{"timestamp":" 946899270902"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama hawa walikula mimea yao yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" YAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899271480","data":{"timestamp":" 946899271480"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama hawa walikula mimea yao yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899273934","data":{"timestamp":" 946899273933"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata waliwabeba watoto na kuwaondosha pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899275128","data":{"timestamp":" 946899275128"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata waliwabeba watoto na kuwaondosha pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIWABEBA"," userResponse":" WALIWABEBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899276169","data":{"timestamp":" 946899276169"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata waliwabeba watoto na kuwaondosha pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899276402","data":{"timestamp":" 946899276402"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata waliwabeba watoto na kuwaondosha pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899277525","data":{"timestamp":" 946899277524"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata waliwabeba watoto na kuwaondosha pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAONDOSHA"," userResponse":" KUWAONDOSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899277932","data":{"timestamp":" 946899277931"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata waliwabeba watoto na kuwaondosha pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899280957","data":{"timestamp":" 946899280956"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa pahali pazuri pa kuishi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPAKUWA"," userResponse":" HAPAKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899281638","data":{"timestamp":" 946899281638"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa pahali pazuri pa kuishi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAHALI"," userResponse":" PAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899282399","data":{"timestamp":" 946899282399"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa pahali pazuri pa kuishi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAZURI"," userResponse":" PAZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899282623","data":{"timestamp":" 946899282622"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa pahali pazuri pa kuishi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PA"," userResponse":" PA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899283334","data":{"timestamp":" 946899283334"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa pahali pazuri pa kuishi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUISHI"," userResponse":" KUISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899283957","data":{"timestamp":" 946899283957"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa pahali pazuri pa kuishi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899286655","data":{"timestamp":" 946899286655"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wangeenda wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899287462","data":{"timestamp":" 946899287461"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wangeenda wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGEENDA"," userResponse":" WANGEENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899288385","data":{"timestamp":" 946899288384"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wangeenda wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" WAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899291622","data":{"timestamp":" 946899291622"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia moja ilipata jibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899292201","data":{"timestamp":" 946899292201"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia moja ilipata jibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899293144","data":{"timestamp":" 946899293144"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia moja ilipata jibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIPATA"," userResponse":" ILIPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899293728","data":{"timestamp":" 946899293728"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia moja ilipata jibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIBU"," userResponse":" JIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899297018","data":{"timestamp":" 946899297017"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haikuwa vigumu kupata chakula milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAIKUWA"," userResponse":" HAIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899297795","data":{"timestamp":" 946899297794"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haikuwa vigumu kupata chakula milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIGUMU"," userResponse":" VIGUMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899298497","data":{"timestamp":" 946899298497"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haikuwa vigumu kupata chakula milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPATA"," userResponse":" KUPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899299319","data":{"timestamp":" 946899299319"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haikuwa vigumu kupata chakula milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899300490","data":{"timestamp":" 946899300490"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haikuwa vigumu kupata chakula milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MILIMANI"," userResponse":" MILIMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899303497","data":{"timestamp":" 946899303497"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vichaka vilimea katikati mwa pengo za miamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VICHAKA"," userResponse":" VICHAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899304400","data":{"timestamp":" 946899304400"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vichaka vilimea katikati mwa pengo za miamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILIMEA"," userResponse":" VILIMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899305485","data":{"timestamp":" 946899305483"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vichaka vilimea katikati mwa pengo za miamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" KATIKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899305809","data":{"timestamp":" 946899305809"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vichaka vilimea katikati mwa pengo za miamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWA"," userResponse":" MWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899306440","data":{"timestamp":" 946899306440"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vichaka vilimea katikati mwa pengo za miamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENGO"," userResponse":" PENGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899306705","data":{"timestamp":" 946899306704"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vichaka vilimea katikati mwa pengo za miamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899307501","data":{"timestamp":" 946899307499"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vichaka vilimea katikati mwa pengo za miamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIAMBA"," userResponse":" MIAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899310008","data":{"timestamp":" 946899310008"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miti ilimea kwenye mitelemko ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITI"," userResponse":" MITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899310811","data":{"timestamp":" 946899310811"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miti ilimea kwenye mitelemko ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIMEA"," userResponse":" ILIMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899311303","data":{"timestamp":" 946899311303"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miti ilimea kwenye mitelemko ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899311827","data":{"timestamp":" 946899311827"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Miti ilimea kwenye mitelemko ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899311908","data":{"timestamp":" 946899311908"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miti ilimea kwenye mitelemko ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.116","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899317378","data":{"timestamp":" 946899317377"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 984bc178-0423-4f9a-afc9-7f47036ac0ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Miti ilimea kwenye mitelemko ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899322100","data":{"timestamp":" 946899322100"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 2c114aa8-dedf-4834-ae2b-076aa6426df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899336846","data":{"timestamp":" 946899336845"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 2c114aa8-dedf-4834-ae2b-076aa6426df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" END"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899339572","data":{"timestamp":" 946899339570"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 2c114aa8-dedf-4834-ae2b-076aa6426df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899339753","data":{"timestamp":" 946899339753"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 2c114aa8-dedf-4834-ae2b-076aa6426df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.116","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899345796","data":{"timestamp":" 946899345795"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 2c114aa8-dedf-4834-ae2b-076aa6426df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899354404","data":{"timestamp":" 946899354404"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 2c114aa8-dedf-4834-ae2b-076aa6426df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.116","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899362156","data":{"timestamp":" 946899362156"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 2c114aa8-dedf-4834-ae2b-076aa6426df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899392095","data":{"timestamp":" 946899392095"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 0251b686-b693-4cdf-ab38-7cd39a20cb19"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v9"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899394115","data":{"timestamp":" 946899394115"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 0251b686-b693-4cdf-ab38-7cd39a20cb19"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v9"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899398368","data":{"timestamp":" 946899398368"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 0251b686-b693-4cdf-ab38-7cd39a20cb19"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_5v4"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899399894","data":{"timestamp":" 946899399894"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 0251b686-b693-4cdf-ab38-7cd39a20cb19"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_5v4"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899406270","data":{"timestamp":" 946899406270"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 0251b686-b693-4cdf-ab38-7cd39a20cb19"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v8"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899410496","data":{"timestamp":" 946899410496"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 0251b686-b693-4cdf-ab38-7cd39a20cb19"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_1v2"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899413864","data":{"timestamp":" 946899413863"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 0251b686-b693-4cdf-ab38-7cd39a20cb19"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_1v2"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899418439","data":{"timestamp":" 946899418439"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 0251b686-b693-4cdf-ab38-7cd39a20cb19"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_5v2"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899422240","data":{"timestamp":" 946899422240"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 0251b686-b693-4cdf-ab38-7cd39a20cb19"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v8"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899426655","data":{"timestamp":" 946899426655"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 0251b686-b693-4cdf-ab38-7cd39a20cb19"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v8"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899432792","data":{"timestamp":" 946899432792"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 0251b686-b693-4cdf-ab38-7cd39a20cb19"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v9"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899438689","data":{"timestamp":" 946899438689"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 0251b686-b693-4cdf-ab38-7cd39a20cb19"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v5"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899442439","data":{"timestamp":" 946899442439"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 0251b686-b693-4cdf-ab38-7cd39a20cb19"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ND_8v5"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.116","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899448459","data":{"timestamp":" 946899448458"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 0251b686-b693-4cdf-ab38-7cd39a20cb19"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ND_8v5"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899457758","data":{"timestamp":" 946899457758"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 0251b686-b693-4cdf-ab38-7cd39a20cb19"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ND_8v5"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:U..U.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.117","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899463120","data":{"timestamp":" 946899463120"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 0251b686-b693-4cdf-ab38-7cd39a20cb19"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ND_8v5"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899472429","data":{"timestamp":" 946899472429"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" a5692ef7-e7cd-47de-b52a-d694153dd81a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-8"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899473794","data":{"timestamp":" 946899473793"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" a5692ef7-e7cd-47de-b52a-d694153dd81a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-8"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:U..U.all.10.rand.say.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899496264","data":{"timestamp":" 946899496264"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 73e279ba-d9f1-4c82-ab3b-abf20148205a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_U..U.all.10.rand.say.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_e_u_y"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:U..U.all.10.rand.say.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899502918","data":{"timestamp":" 946899502918"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 73e279ba-d9f1-4c82-ab3b-abf20148205a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_U..U.all.10.rand.say.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_u_t_m"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:U..U.all.10.rand.say.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899510461","data":{"timestamp":" 946899510461"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 73e279ba-d9f1-4c82-ab3b-abf20148205a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_U..U.all.10.rand.say.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_u_t_m"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:U..U.all.10.rand.say.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899517119","data":{"timestamp":" 946899517119"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 73e279ba-d9f1-4c82-ab3b-abf20148205a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_U..U.all.10.rand.say.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_l_z_u"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:U..U.all.10.rand.say.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899523778","data":{"timestamp":" 946899523778"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 73e279ba-d9f1-4c82-ab3b-abf20148205a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_U..U.all.10.rand.say.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_g_u_z"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:U..U.all.10.rand.say.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899524866","data":{"timestamp":" 946899524866"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 73e279ba-d9f1-4c82-ab3b-abf20148205a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_U..U.all.10.rand.say.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_g_u_z"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899532533","data":{"timestamp":" 946899532532"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 73e279ba-d9f1-4c82-ab3b-abf20148205a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_U..U.all.10.rand.say.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_g_u_z"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899539139","data":{"timestamp":" 946899539138"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 73e279ba-d9f1-4c82-ab3b-abf20148205a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_U..U.all.10.rand.say.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_g_u_z"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899547497","data":{"timestamp":" 946899547496"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 73e279ba-d9f1-4c82-ab3b-abf20148205a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_U..U.all.10.rand.say.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_g_u_z"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899552987","data":{"timestamp":" 946899552987"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 73e279ba-d9f1-4c82-ab3b-abf20148205a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_U..U.all.10.rand.say.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_g_u_z"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899559857","data":{"timestamp":" 946899559857"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 73e279ba-d9f1-4c82-ab3b-abf20148205a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_U..U.all.10.rand.say.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_g_u_z"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899566908","data":{"timestamp":" 946899566908"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 73e279ba-d9f1-4c82-ab3b-abf20148205a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_U..U.all.10.rand.say.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_g_u_z"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899575369","data":{"timestamp":" 946899575369"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_143345"," gameId":" 73e279ba-d9f1-4c82-ab3b-abf20148205a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_U..U.all.10.rand.say.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_g_u_z"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}